//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
        {
            numb: 1,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character ま make?",
            answer: "ma",
            options: ["mi", "ma", "mu", "me"]
        },
        {
            numb: 2,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character み make?",
            answer: "mi",
            options: ["me", "mi", "ma", "mu"]
        },
        {
            numb: 3,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character む make?",
            answer: "mu",
            options: ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me"]
        },
        {
            numb: 4,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character め make?",
            answer: "me",
            options: ["mu", "mi", "me", "ma"]
        },
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character も make?",
            answer: "mo",
            options: ["ma", "mi", "mo", "mu"]
        },
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character や make?",
            answer: "ya",
            options: ["yu", "yo", "ye", "ya"]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character ゆ make?",
            answer: "yu",
            options: ["yo", "yu", "ye", "ya"]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character よ make?",
            answer: "yo",
            options: ["yo", "yu", "ye", "ya"]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character ら make?",
            answer: "ra",
            options: ["ri", "ra", "re", "ru"]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character り make?",
            answer: "ri",
            options: ["ri", "ra", "ru", "re"]
        },
        {
            numb: 11,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character る make?",
            answer: "ru",
            options: ["ru", "ri", "re", "ra"]
        },
        {
            numb: 12,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character れ make?",
            answer: "re",
            options: ["ri", "re", "ra", "ru"]
        },
        {
            numb: 13,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character ろ make?",
            answer: "ro",
            options: ["ro", "ri", "re", "ru"]
        },
        {
            numb: 14,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character わ make?",
            answer: "wa",
            options: ["wo", "wa", "we", "wi"]
        },
        {
            numb: 15,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character を make?",
            answer: "wo",
            options: ["wo", "wa", "we", "wi"]
        },
        {
            numb: 16,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character ん make?",
            answer: "n",
            options: ["no", "na", "ne", "n"]
        },
        {
            numb: 17,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word すし ?",
            answer: "sushi",
            options: ["sasu", "sushi", "susu", "sese"]
        },
        {
            numb: 18,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word とり (bird)?",
            answer: "tori",
            options: ["tori", "toriu", "tora", "toro"]
        },
        {
            numb: 19,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word いぬ (dog)?",
            answer: "inu",
            options: ["ino", "inu", "eni", "in"]
        },
        {
            numb: 20,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word ねこ (cat)?",
            answer: "neko",
            options: ["neko", "noka", "nani", "nemo"]
        },
        {
            numb: 21,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word はな (flower)?",
            answer: "hana",
            options: ["hana", "hane", "hama", "hanae"]
        },
        {
            numb: 22,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word くるま (car)?",
            answer: "kuruma",
            options: ["koruma", "kuruma", "kurana", "karuma"]
        },
        {
            numb: 23,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word そと (outside)?",
            answer: "soto",
            options: ["soto", "soko", "sato", "sora"]
        },
        {
            numb: 24,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word やま (mountain)?",
            answer: "yama",
            options: ["yama", "yamae", "yomi", "yamu"]
        },
        {
            numb: 25,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word ゆき (snow)?",
            answer: "yuki",
            options: ["yume", "yuki", "yumi", "yuri"]
        },
        {
            numb: 26,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word あめ (rain)?",
            answer: "ame",
            options: ["anu", "ame", "ami", "ane"]
        },
        
        {
          numb: 27,
         question: "What is the romaji for the word さくら (cherry blossom)?",
           answer: "sakura",
           options: ["sakura", "saku", "sari", "sake"]
        },
    
        {
            numb: 28,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word うみ (sea)?",
            answer: "umi",
            options: ["umi", "uni", "ume", "uma"]
        },
        {
            numb: 29,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word えき (station)?",
            answer: "eki",
            options: ["eiki", "eki", "eka", "eka"]
        },
        {
            numb: 30,
            question: "What is the romaji for the word しろ (white)?",
            answer: "shiro",
            options: ["shiro", "shiri", "siro", "shiru"]
        },
    ];
    
    